SERGEY SAPRANKOV

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



Belarus, Zhlobin City

@gmail 🖴

My portfolio website

+375(29) 355-86-03

My github (7)



PROFILE

Hi there! I am a Front-end developer. I have experience in creating a SPA, from scratch, with webpack setup and all dependencies (Webpack / React / Redux / TS). Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies (Next JS). Ready to consider project work and full-time employment

EXPERIENCES

Jan 2022 - present day Project work frontend developer (part-time) Key responsibilities:

- Creating SPA on React & Redux & TypeScript
- Development new components and pages with React &
- Working with the server using ajax (CRUD determination and data processing)
- RESTful (registration / loginization / pagination)
- Created UI-kit (table, dashboards, buttons, forms, modal windows, etc)
- Optimization | Lazy loading | Bundle analysis
- · Fix errors and bugs
- · CSS modules and theming
- Storybook and screenshot tests
- Team development

My project:

- Learning cards app learning app in team work. Technologies: TS, React, Redux Toolkit, React hook form, Yup, React Router Dom, Axios, Material UI, Git. Click to view the project
- To Do List app classic task manager app. Technologies: TS, React, Redux Toolkit, React hook form, Yup, React Router Dom, Axios, Ant design, Git.

Click to view the project

• Blog Platform - in progress.

Jul 2014 - present day Process automation based on logic controllers **Key responsibilities:**

- Development of a program based on logic controllers.
- Development of visualization tools for managing the state of the technological process.

EDUCATION

IT INCUBATOR

2022 - 2023 | React, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript

HTML ACADEMY

2020-2021 | HTML, CSS, JS

SUKHOI TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY, **GOMEL**

2009-2014 | Electrical Engineer. Automated electric drives

SKILLS

- React | Redux
- JavaScript | Typescript
- React-Router-Dom | Redux-Thunk/Redux-Saga | Formik | Axios
- Material UI | Ant Design
- HTTP | HTTPS | Rest API
- HTML | CSS | SASS (BEM)
- Jest | StoryBook | TDD | Postman
- Git | GitHub

LANGUAGES

Russian native language

English Pre-Intermediate (in

progress)